That is the, it's such a, oh, what a dumb question.
The illegal aliens who are here
are taking jobs away from blacks.
They're taking jobs away from whites.
They're taking jobs away from Latinos.
They're taking their health benefits away.
They're taking their school slots away.
And of course, in many cases,
they're committing heinous crimes.
We cannot have a system of law in this country
that privileges illegal aliens over American citizens.
And that's what they're doing.
You know it, and I know it.
So that's not exactly a no, Stephen.
Can you just unequivocally state
that the immigration policy-
I said it's a dumb question.
Okay, no, and it's a dumb question.